(Leonard:)Morning.
(Leonard:)You're making eggs for breakfast?
(Sheldon:)This isn't breakfast, it's an experiment.
Oh. Because it looks a lot like breakfast.
I finally have time to test my hypothesis
about the separation of water molecules...
(Sheldon:)...from the egg proteins
and its impact vis-à-vis taste.
(Leonard:)Sounds yummy.
(Leonard:)I look forward to your work with bacon.
(Sheldon:)As do I.
You know, I'm sure if you just apologize
to Gablehauser he'd give your job back.
(Sheldon:)I don't want my job back.
I've spent three and a half years
staring at grease boards full of equations.
(Sheldon:)Before that,
I spent four years working on my thesis.
(Sheldon:)Before that, I was in college,
and before that I was in the fifth grade.
(Sheldon:)This is my first day off in decades
and I'm going to savor it.
(Leonard:)Okay. I'll let you get back
to fixing your eggs.
(Sheldon:)I'm not just fixing my eggs,
I'm fixing everyone's eggs.